devhub.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy - DevHub

Protecting your privacy and the personal information you provide us is a top priority at DevHub. For this reason, DevHub does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. At DevHub, we want our users to fully understand what information we collect, how we use this information, and the steps we take to protect your personal information. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the policies and procedures DevHub has put in place to achieve this goal. In addition, DevHub wants our users to feel comfortable that we take all necessary steps to protect their personal information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact DevHub's Privacy Department by emailing info@devhub.com, calling 206-441-4399, or writing DevHub at 2101 4th Ave., Suite 350, Seattle, WA.

## Overview

The privacy practices of this statement apply to the services provided by DevHub available under the domain and subdomains of www.DevHub.com (the"site") and apply generally to our affiliates. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our site.

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you and what may happen to that information as part of the normal operation of our services. DevHub strives to provide a consistent set of privacy practices across an international community, and as such, all of our affiliates operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy, subject to the requirements of applicable law.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement at the point of registration, you expressly consent to DevHub's use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the DevHub User Agreement. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on February 10, 2009 for all users.

## Information from Children

If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians, and with express permission from DevHub. For this reason, we ask that children do not submit any personal information to DevHub.

## Information We Collect

DevHub only collects personal information about users that we consider necessary for providing our services in an efficient, customized, and user-friendly manner, including your name, address, phone number, email address, and/or payment address.

## Our Use of Your Information

In general, you can browse a large portion of the site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the site. You always have the option not to provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you register for a user account but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us you can indicate your preference on the registration form. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at contact (at) DevHub.com or you may call us at +1 206 441 4399.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider so that you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

Under some circumstances we may require some additional financial information, including, without limitation, your billing address, bank account information, a credit card number and expiration date, and tracking information from checks or money orders.

We may automatically collect certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to serve our users better. This information may include the URL that you come from or go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We may offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie." We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information targeted to your interests. Personally identifiable information you have submitted while on our site is linked with information gathered from our use of cookies in the form of log files. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the site and you may be required to re-enter your password or provide other information more frequently during a session.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) may use "cookies" sites created on our platform. We have no access to or control over these "cookies." This privacy statement covers the use of "cookies" by DevHub only and does not cover the use of "cookies" by any advertisers.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on the site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

We use your information and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, collect fees owed, pay amounts due you, verify your account data, measure user interest in DevHub's products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates, customize your experience, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and we may examine your information to identify users using multiple Login Names. We may compare and review your information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your perceived interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the site. By accepting this Agreement, you expressly agree to receive this information.

## Our Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal course of business as part of our services.

Advertisers. We aggregate (gather up data across numerous registered user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. For such purposes, we do not disclose any information that could be used to identify DevHub users personally.

Affiliates for Our Operations. We may use third parties ("affiliates") to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the services that we provide to you and therefore we may provide some of your information directly to these affiliates. These affiliates are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced service, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the affiliate may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the affiliate, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be up to you.

Agents and Business Entities. We share much of our data, including personal information about you, with our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint venturers that are committed to serving your online needs and providing related services throughout the world. We use an outside credit card processing company or Paypal to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint venturers follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. DevHub, its affiliates, subsidiaries, joint venturers, or any combination of such, will share some or all of your information with another business entity should we plan to merge with, or be acquired by, that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your information.

Legal Requests. DevHub cooperates with law enforcement authorities, as well as with other third parties, to enforce laws, intellectual property rights, and to prevent fraud. In response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, login name history, fraud complaints, and site use history, with or without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, we will not disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to protect our rights or to prevent imminent physical harm, financial loss or to report suspected past, present, or future illegal activity. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose to a third party your information, including your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

## Your Use of Other Users' Information

In order to facilitate interaction among site users, our site may allows you limited access to other users' activities on your site for reporting purposes. By entering into our User Agreement, you agree that, with respect to other users' personal information that you obtain through the site or through a DevHub-related communication or DevHub-facilitated transaction, DevHub hereby grants to you a limited, non-transferable, revocable license to use such information only for: (a) DevHub-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, (b) using services offered through DevHub, and (c) any other purpose that a user expressly agrees to after you tell them the purpose you would like to use it for. In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined herein, can you disclose personal information about another site user to any third party without the written consent of DevHub and the written consent of that user, including, but not limited to, email correspondence with DevHub staff regarding DevHub users, whether in the course of providing DevHub services or otherwise. You agree that other users may use your personal information to communicate with you in accordance with this paragraph.

## Policy against advertising our website using unsolicited email messages

We require that all e-mails promoting devhub.com, rallymind.com, cloudbackend.net or cloudfrontend.net or its products are sent only to clients who have agreed to receive such messages. We prohibit any advertising of our brand and Web site using unsolicited email messages. Not complying with this policy will cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination.

If you feel you’ve been sent unsolicited emails promoting our brand or website and would like to register a complaint, please email our abuse department (abuse@devhub.com). We will immediately investigate all allegations made related to unsolicited messages.

If you feel you’ve been sent unsolicited email and would like to register a complaint, please email our abuse department (abuse@devhub.com).

## Control of Your Login Name and Password

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login name and password, including fees charged to your account and adherence to the Acceptable Use terms contained in the DevHub User Agreement. Your DevHub user password should be held in strict confidence and under no circumstances will DevHub personnel, its agents or affiliates ask you for your DevHub user password. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password as detailed in the paragraph below.

## Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

We offer you the ability to review and change the information you submit to us by logging into the site and entering in the new information yourself. Once logged in as a registered user, you can change your Password, other personal, contact, and financial information, and user. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once posted, you may not be able to change or remove any bids or postings made on the site.

Generally, we will not modify your personal information based on a request not submitted through the site because it can be difficult to authenticate your identity manually.

Upon your request, we will deactivate and delete your account, contact information, billing information, shipping information, and financial information from our active databases. To make this request, email info (at) DevHub.com. Your account will be deactivated and deleted as soon as reasonably possible after we receive your request but no later than 30 days.

Upon receipt of a deactivation request, we will retain some of your information in order to prevent fraud, collect fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our User Agreement, and comply with legal requirements. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, your information will be deactivated from our active, registered user database, and will only be available to select DevHub personnel.

## Discussion Boards

If you use the discussion boards located on our site you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. DevHub is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

## Other Information Collectors

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. DevHub does not control the privacy policies of third parties.

## Security

DevHub follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Your information is stored on DevHub's servers located in the United. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card or bank information) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company, but "perfect security "does not exist on the Internet or with any data, digital or physical.

DevHub personnel receive training on complying with our privacy practices and the importance of protecting your information. Disciplinary procedures are in place in should a DevHub employee violate our Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about security on our web site, you can email us at info (at) DevHub.com.

## Changing Our Privacy Practices

Please note that because of the changing nature of privacy laws, consumer needs, and our business, DevHub is committed to the constant monitoring and examination of its privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any material changes are made to the company's privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this privacy policy and we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. Regardless of any future changes, however, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.

Effective Date: 10/26/2016  
Posting Date: 10/26/2016
